Mizuno!
水野！
She gets scared “pyon pyon,” and frightens easily, “pyon, doki-doki, pyon!”
怯えてピョンピョン、怖がりピョン ドキドキピョン
Are you trying to gain height by jumping?
ジャンプで身長かせいでる？
Yui has already gotten bigger this way!
由結は、こんなに大きくなったもん！
Kikuchi!
菊地！
An idol-obsessed idol, a miniature adult
アイドルだけどアイドルオタク　ちっちゃい大人
Meanwhile there’s a warning being issued for this little devil
小悪魔警報発令中
Beware of Moa!
最愛にご・注・意！
Notsu!
野津！
Even as she smiles, she spits poison; she is a steadfast offender
ニコニコしながら毒を吐く！確信犯
What’s the phrase she personally devised?
自ら名付けたあだ名は？
Fake honor student!
にせ優等生！
Taguchi!
田口！
In her right hand, “lettuce,” in her left, “a radish,” she takes a bite
右手に 「レタス」 左に 「大根」 かじりつく
When both her arms come together, “cross chop!”
両手合わせて 「クロスチョップ」
Hey, Hana, thoughts on today?
ねぇ、華、今日の感想は？
Normal.
普通です.
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us, “Are you following?”
ちょちょちょ　私のこと 「わかってんの〜？ 」
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
見た目とのギャップが魅力
Observe the steady progress of our feminine power!
日進月歩　見てろっ　この女子力
Let’s strive to become Super Ladies!
目指せ！ ス — パ — レディ — を
Shirai!
白井！
She’d commute to concerts out of her own pocket
自腹でライブに通ってました
And I bought all the merch!
グッズも全部買いました！
She realized her dream, the destined fukei
夢を叶えた元父兄
I love Sakura Gakuin!
さくら学院大好き！！
Isono!
磯野！
Born from the genius star, she fell to Earth and was raised on reggae
天才星で生まれ落ちた レゲエ育ち
She’s known to speak casually, even to vicious-looking folk
悪そうな奴にもだいたい タメグチ
Huh? I’m not sure what you mean
えっ　意味わかんな〜い
Ooga!
大賀！
If you please, your exciting self-introduction “Right!”
手に汗握る自己紹介　よろしくね 「はいっ！ 」
Will you look down on us? Or upward?
目線は上から？下から？
I’ll look up!
下から行くよ — っ！
Yamaide!
山出！
She commutes from Kagoshima prefecture “It’s difficult!”
鹿児島県から通ってます 「大変でごわす！ 」
She’s our dear child who came down from the mountains
山から出てきた　愛しい子供です
Yamaide, who looks like you could beat them at arm-wrestling?
山出、誰だったら腕相撲勝てそう？
Hmm… Hana-chan!
う〜ん、華ちゃん！
Woah! Really?
え！ まじか！
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us “Are you looking on intently?”
ねぇねぇねぇ　私のこと 「ちゃんと見えてますか？ 」
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
見た目とのギャップが魅力
All worldly things are but ephemeral,  Let’s brush up on our feminine power!
諸行無常　磨こっ　その女子力
Let’s strive to become Super Ladies!
目指せ！ ス — パ — レディ — を
Then, I shall call the roll!
それでは 出席をとります
Middle school third years, Kikuchi Moa “Smile!”
中等部３年、菊地最愛 「にこっ」
Taguchi Hana “Deyaa!”
田口華 「でやぁ」
Notsu Yunano “What is it?”
野津友那乃 「なんですかぁ」
Mizuno Yui “Hiii”
水野由結 「はぁ～あい」
Middle school second years, Isono Rinon “Genius!”
中等部２年、磯野莉音 「天才」
Ooga Saki “Indeed!”
大賀咲希 「ぞ」
Shirai Saki “Sakura Gakuin!”
白井沙樹 「さくら学院」
Middle school first year, Kurashima Sara “Here!”
中等部１年、倉島颯良 「は — い」
Elementary school sixth years, Okada Megumi “Here am I!”
小等部６年、岡田愛 「ござる」
Yamaide Aiko “Yes, sir!”
山出愛子 「イエッサ — 」
Well then, remaining members, please introduce yourselves!
それでは 残りのメンバ — の 自己紹介 よろしく！
Um.. Who is it again? Oh, right! Kurashima!
え〜っっと、あっ、倉島！
She deals sternly with her homeroom teacher, who forgets her name
名前を忘れる担任には　厳しくいくぞ
Kurashima the magician, with her illusions
マジシャン　倉島　イリュ — ジョン
Those who do not remember will be vanished!
覚えてくれないと消しちゃいますよ！
Okada!
岡田！
From Mikawa province she has invaded, a knowledgeable history buff
三河の国から　攻め込んだ　物知り歴女
Megu knows! I know!
めぐ知ってる！ 知ってる！
She is wont to quote samurai while she spins
回転しながら、偉人の名言　言います
Today, I am Tokugawa Ieyasu-san!
今日は徳川家康さんです
Tighten the string of the kabuto (helmet worn by samurai) after winning the war! (Note: It figuratively means"Don't lower your efforts after succeeding.")
勝って兜の緒を締めろ
Have you studied this yet, everyone?
皆さん、勉強なったでしょ？
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us, “Do you get it now?”
ちょちょちょ　私のこと 「わかってますか？ 」
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
見た目とのギャップが魅力
Observe the steady progress of our feminine power!
日進月歩　見てろっ　この女子力
Let’s strive to become Super Ladies!
目指せ！ ス — パ — レディ — を
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us, “We’ll tell you!”
ねぇねぇねぇ　私のこと 「教えてあげます」
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
見た目とのギャップが魅力
All worldly things are but ephemeral, let’s brush up on our feminine power!
諸行無常　磨こっ　その女子力
Let’s strive to become Super Ladies!
目指せ！ ス — パ — レディ — を
In conclusion, we are the “Limited to the growth period” unit,
以上！ 私たち成長期限定ユニット
Sakura Gakuin!
さくら学院です！